glpi-project.org 2019-07-25

# Privacy Policy - GLPI Project

## Who we are

Our website address is: https://glpi-project.org.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

Sending us an email or subscribing to our Newsletter mailings you are giving your consent to receive communication emails from GLPI and Teclib.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Who we share your data with

The personal information collected on our website is saved in a Teclib’ file, that is managed as part of its statutory purpose.  
The collected information is subject to a data processing, in order to manage the diffusion of publications and the contacts’ file of Teclib’. As such, they are likely to be communicated in whole or part to the different internal services of the company.

Under the above act, you are entitled:  
– To object to processing of personal data of which that individual is the data subject, for legitimate reasons.  
– To object, at no cost, to the use of the data relating to you for purposes of canvassing, in particular for commercial, by the current controller or further data processing.  
– To question the controller in order to obtain:  
* confirmation as to whether or not personal data are processed and stored on a file  
* information (provided on the purposes of the processing of the data), the categories of personal data stored, and the recipients or classes of recipients to whom they are disclosed.  
* communication, in an intangible form, of the personal data relating to you and any available information as to their source.  
– According to the law of rectification, to demand the administration of the file depending on the situation, to correct, complete, update or delete personal data about you which is inaccurate, incomplete, misleading, outdated or whose the collection, use, disclosure or storage is prohibited.

Teclib’ will not sell, trade or share your personal details (such as name, telephone number, postal and e-mail addresses), with any third party outside of the organization.

We draw your attention to the fact that certain information gathered is necessary not only for the conclusion of contracts and benefits offered by Teclib’ but also for their proper implementation. When collecting information, you are informed of the mandatory or optional answers you have to provide.

To exercise these rights, we invite you to send a letter to the following address:  
Teclib’  
Carrer d’Aribau 112 – Planta 5  
08036 Barcelona  
Spain

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Your contact information

Teclib’ commits itself to respect your private life and to protect your rights during the use of the website. However and in order to provide you with the services offered on the website, Teclib’ will have to collect some of your personally identifiable information (only the information we need to answer your request).

Also, sending us an email or subscribing to our Newsletter mailings you are giving your consent to receive communication emails from GLPI and Teclib.

## Additional information

### How we protect your data

Teclib’ is committed to best practice privacy protection on its website (the information is stored in a secured non-public environment). Teclib’ uses measures and industry-standard security protocols to ensure the safety of your personal data, such as encryption, access controls and network firewall while you are visiting our website.  
Please keep in mind that Teclib’ cannot guaranty a total safety while you are surfing on the Internet. From the moment you share your information with anyone, copies of that information can be made, stored, and shared outside our website.

### Cookies and IP address

During your visit to the website, https://glpi-project.org/ may use cookies.  
A cookie is a small piece of data in which a website administrator saves important data for him to facilitate and improve navigation on the website. When browsing our site, information about your browsing may be recorded or read in “Cookie” files installed on your computer, tablet or smartphone.

Cookies are used for:  
The information banner about the use of cookies. The information banner on the presence of cookies and cookies management options on our site are managed by cookie. The purpose of this cookie is to enable the display of this information banner when you first visit the site.

To perform visitors’ statistics. Cookies allow us to know the amount of visits to our site, the amount of viewed pages, the browser used, etc. This information enables us to improve the site (ergonomics, etc.). Those data are not personalized.

To improve technical functions of our site. Cookies allow us to change the language of our site and enable you to send the contact form.

To suggest relevant ads. Cookies are used to analyze your interests to offer you personalized ads.

How to delete cookies?. You can disable cookies. Your browser also can be set to alert you about cookies stored in your computer and ask you to accept it or not. We remind you that settings may alter your conditions of access to services requiring the use of cookies.

You can disable cookies by following the following instructions:  
_Internet explorer_ : In Internet Explorer, click “Tools” then

“Internet Options.” Under the “General” tab, under “Browsing history,” click “Settings.” Click the “View Files”. Click the column header “Name” to sort all files alphabetically, and then scroll down until you see the files beginning with the prefix “Cookie” (all cookies have that prefix and usually contain the name of the website that created the cookie). Select cookies containing the name “https://glpi-project.org/” and delete them. Close the window that contains the file list, and click OK twice to return to Internet Explorer. Details, update: see the browser’s help page: <http://windows.microsoft.com/fr-> FR/windows-vista/Block- or-allow- cookies

_Firefox_ : Go to the “Tools” from the browser and select the “Options” tab. In the window that appears, choose “Privacy” and click “Show Cookies”. In the window that appears, choose “Privacy” and click “Show Cookies” Locate the files that contain the name “https://glpi-project.org/” select them and delete them. Details, update: see the browser’s help page: <http://support.mozilla.org/fr>

_Safari Help page_ : In your browser, select the “Edit > Preferences” menu. Click on “Security”. Click “Show Cookies”. Select the cookies that contain the name “https://glpi-project.org/” and click “Delete” or “Clear All”. After deleting cookies, click “Done”. Details, update: see the browser’s help page: <http://docs.info.apple.com/>

_Google Chrome Help page_ : Click on the icon of the “Tools” menu. Select “Options”. Click the “Advanced Options” tab and go to the “Privacy” section. Click the “Show Cookies”. Locate the files that contain the name “https://glpi-project.org/” Select them and delete them. Click “Close” to return to your browser. ”

## Copying

  * **Name** : [GLPI](http://glpi-project.org/) is a registered trademark of [Teclib’](http://www.teclib-edition.com/en/).
  * **Code** : you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License ([GPLv3](https://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.en.html)).
  * **Documentation** : released under Attribution 4.0 International ([CC BY 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/)).

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Website Owner: Teclib’  
Avenida Diagonal, 440 – Planta 5  
08037 Barcelona  
Spain  
Director of the company: Pascal Aubry  
Spanish company registration number (CIF): B66366337
